# Mary Angelita Rocha Wilches

Cel: 510 926 1608 ♦ Maryrocha79@gmail.com

# PROFESSIONAL BACKGROUND

Fourteen years of experience as a costumer service in different sectors of the economy, as financial, families, and health and Fitness. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. Proven ability to establish rapport with clients and exceed expectations. Adaptable and driven, with strong time management and prioritization abilities. Strong problem solving aptitude following company guidelines.

### JOB EXPERIENCE

Fitness Evolves
Head Personal Trainer
July 2012-Currently

Responsible for designing customized training programs based upon fitness goals, specific injuries or health problems for 100% of clients.

Maintain detailed personal training records and updated progress after each session for each client served.

Measure clients' overall fitness by completing comprehensive evaluations and physician clearances.

Responsible for processing clients satisfaction evaluations at the end of each phase of their program.

Consistently improve fitness center revenue targets by developing new programs and retaining clients

Berkeley Ironworks Personal Trainer Jan 2009- May 2012

Developed safe and effective exercise programs for all members.

Assessed individual progress and suggested appropriate changes.

Taught a variety of group exercise classes.

Consistently met daily class attendance goals.

Bancolombia Senior Bank Teller June 2002– Nov 2005

Established new customer accounts including checking, savings, lines of credit and loans.

Coordinated daily cash reconciliation at a high-volume location.

Maintained balancing record with 100% rate of accuracy.

Prepared customer and ATM cash and change orders.

Trained employees on cash drawer operation.

# **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

Industrial Engineer
Distrital Francisco Jose de Caldas University March 2003

Certified Personal Trainer National Academy of Sports Medicine March 2009

Certified Coach R,I,T & S Z - Health Performance March 2015

# **LANGUAGES**

English and Spanish